#### Contact

jnjcater@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jeffery-cater-rn-bsn-cen-735b9685 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Hospitals

**Business** 

Compassion

### Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)

### Certifications

Certified Emergency Nurse
Advance Cardiac Life Support
Neonatal Resuscitation Program
Registered Nurse

# Jeffery Cater RN, BSN, CEN

Flight Nurse at California Shock Trauma Air Rescue (CALSTAR) Ukiah, California

## Summary

I am a graduate from the University of Washington, with a Bachelors in Nursing (BSN), and licensed in WA, OR and CA. I have a real passion and desire for wanting to help people through my nursing skills. I would love the opportunity to become part of your Hospital/ Organization where I can gain new experiences and further my knowledge as a registered nurse. I will utilize and enhance my knowledge and skills to provide quality patient care and grow as a professional nurse for your organization. I have also increased my knowledge by becoming a Certified Emergency Nurse (CEN) in order to make me better asset to your organization. I am a highly motivated, energetic individual who takes the initiative in getting the job done. I enjoy working in a busy environment (Emergency Room) where I am able to utilize my skills. I am a self-starter, and look forward to challenges. I want to help fix the problem, not cause it. I am very compassionate about my chosen profession, as patient care and safety are number one importance to me.

## Experience

California Shock Trauma Air Rescue (CALSTAR)
Flight Nurse
November 2019 - Present (8 months)
Ukiah, CA

REACH Air Medical Services
Flight Nurse
August 2018 - November 2019 (1 year 4 months)
Willitis, Ca

Adventist Health
Emergency Room Registered Nurse
December 2017 - August 2018 (9 months)
Ukiah, CA

United Staffing Solutions, Inc. (USSI) 9 months

Emergency Room Registered Nurse September 2017 - December 2017 (4 months)

Ukiah Valley Medical Center, Ukiah CA

Emergency Room Travel Nurse April 2017 - September 2017 (6 months)

Beverly Hospital Montebello, CA

TravelMax
Emergency Room Travel RN
December 2016 - April 2017 (5 months)
Dayton General Hospital Dayton WA

Skagit Valley Hospital

2 years 1 month

Emergency Room RN-RS

Emergency Room RN-BSN January 2015 - December 2016 (2 years) Mount Vernon, WA

Staff RN -Orthopedics and Surgical Floor December 2014 - April 2015 (5 months) Mount Vernon, WA

Evergreen Medical Center Intensive care/ Emergency Room Nurse July 2014 - June 2015 (1 year) Monroe, WA

Merry Haven Care Center 1 year 7 months

Staff RN May 2014 - January 2015 (9 months) Snohomish, WA

LPN July 2013 - May 2014 (11 months) Snohomish, WA

Sugar Pine Cafe

Manager; Cook; Waiter January 2002 - November 2010 (8 years 11 months) Lapine, Oregon

Harpole Construction
Contractor/Framer/ Construction Worker
June 2002 - November 2007 (5 years 6 months)
Lapine, OR

## Education

University of Washington
Bachelor's Degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2014 - 2015)

Everett Community College
Associate's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2010 - 2014)

Frontier
One Year Bible cert. (2007 - 2008)